http://www.videopoker.com/privacy/settings/

Your Privacy Is Important to Us
We respect your right to privacy and have a Privacy and Cookie Policy in place so you understand what kind of information we collect about you when you visit and play games on our sites and apps.
Click here to read our Privacy Policy
Click here to read our Cookie Policy
Click here to learn more about cookies
Third-Party Data Sharing
Information entered in your VideoPoker.com profile (such as your email address) is not
shared with 3rd parties unless you specifically direct us to do so.
We do not share your personal information outside of VideoPoker.com, although some data may be collected and used by our 3rd party advertising partners.
For visitors and members who see 3rd party ads, VideoPoker.com uses some of the information collected from this site to serve advertisements more relevant to your interests. Occasionally we do this with help from 3rd parties. We understand if you’d rather us not share your information and respect your right to disable this use of your data with our third parties in this browser.
If you would like to learn more about how we share data, please visit our Privacy Policy.
Necessary Cookies
These cookies are necessary for the site to function and cannot be switched off in our systems. They are usually only set in response to actions made by you which amount to a request for services, such as setting your privacy preferences, logging in or filling in forms. You can set your browser to block or alert you about these cookies, but some parts of the site will not then work. These cookies do not store personally identifiable information.
Play
Play authentic video poker just like the casino
Play video-poker
Play keno
VideoKeno.com
Play contests
Find in casinos
Player challenges
Discover new features,
Action Gaming, Inc. - All Rights Reserved.
Privacy Policy CCPA Notice Do Not Sell My Personal Info Cookie Policy Terms Advertise Affiliates Responsible Gambling
This site uses cookies for personalized content and analytics. By continuing to use this site, you agree to this use.
Close
Member Login
Email
Password
Forgot your password?
Create new account
Cancel
